Hiu Mei Fu

UX / UI + Graphic Designer







in linkedin.com/in/mei-fu/ https://meifuux.github.io/

Skills

UI Design User Experience Design (UED)

User Research **Design Systems**

User Flow Design Psychology

Brand Guidelines User Journey

Prototyping Responsive Design

Wireframing Communication

Tools

Adobe XD Figma Sketch InVision

Adobe Creative Suite

(Photoshop, Illustrator, AfterEffects, InDesign, XD)

HTML, CSS & JavaScript

Education

Bachelor of Science In Creative Media

Aug 2015 - Oct 2019 · 3.51 GPA · 1st Honor

City University Of Hong Kong, Hong Kong

Certifications

Google UX Design Professional Certificate

Coursera | Google

Credential ID: 9JDNBHW3KQ9P

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Google

Credential ID: 3EH DR6 67L

Languages

English, Mandarin, Cantonese

Awards

Hong Kong ICT Awards 2020

Certification of Merit, Student Innovation

Profile

I am an aspiring UI/UX & Graphic designer with 2+ years of strong experience in creating user-centered design solutions that solve complex problems. With strong sense of creativity, collaboration and empathy that drive business value and enhance user engagement.

Experience

UX/UI & Graphic Designer

Orange Data Limited • Dec 2022 - Present | Freelance Mar 2022 - Nov 2022 | On-Site | Hong Kong

- · Designed engaging B2C platforms, including website, mobile web, app, for World Entertainment's casino gaming, utilizing UX/UI design principles based on user
- · Increased user engagement by 25% and website traffic by 40% through website redesign and optimization efforts.
- · Created effective marketing and promotional materials to drive B2B & B2C customer interest and increase sales.
- · Collaborated with cross-functional teams using Figma and clear communication to ensure successful project delivery.

Junior Web Designer

Semeiotics Group (Asia) Limited • Mar 2021 - Nov 2021 | On-Site | Hong Kong

- · Revamped website content and design for major clients, including: Gold Peak Technology Group Limited and Genji Kyoto
- · Increased website traffic by 33% and maximized user engagement by implementing effective design strategies.
- · Utilizing UI design best practices and aligning with client business needs and value.
- · Implemented multiple responsive and SEO-optimized websites using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript within CMS platforms such as WordPress and Squarespace. Streamlined website performance.

Technical Artist

SenMedia Limited • Nov 2020 - Mar 2021 | Freelance | Hong Kong

- · Led government website revamp, optimizing information architecture for enhanced user experience with UX/UI design principles.
- \cdot Collaborated with cross-functional teams, including programmers, clients, project manager & the CEO, leveraging teamwork and communication skills for successful project delivery and customer satisfaction.
- · Employed user research and iterative design methods to create user-centered designs that met business goals and needs with data-driven design decisions.
- · Utilized Adobe XD and interactive prototype reviews for efficient design processes and client communication